In the rest of this module,
在本單元的其餘部分，
I'm going to provide a very basic overview of the Python programming language.
我將提供Python程式語言的基本概述。
If you have a background in programming,
如果你有編寫程式的背景，
this overview should be enough to help you be successful in the rest of this course
這個概述應該足以幫助你在本課程的其餘部分
and the following courses in this specialization.
和本專業課程裏的其他課程中取得成功。
If you don't have a programming experience or
如果你沒有編寫程式的經驗，或者
feel like content is overly challenging, then I would encourage you to stop and
覺得內容太過於挑戰，那麼我會鼓勵你暫時停下來，
take an introductory programming class.
並選上一些編寫程式的入門課程。
A colleague of mine, Dr. Chuck Severance offers an excellent specialization on
我的一位同事，Chuck Severance博士為Coursera提供了一個很好的專業課程，
Coursera, called Python for Everybody.
名字為'Python for Everybody'。
You can find a link to that in the course resources.
你可以在Coursera課程資料中找到該連結。
The Coursera system allows you to run Python code from your browser in two ways.
Coursera系統允許你以兩種方式從瀏覽器運行Python的程式。
First, we can use in-video prompts, where a question will come up and
首先，我們可以使用出現在影片內的問題提示，
you can try and solve that question in the browser.
你可以在瀏覽器裏嘗試並解決這個問題。
This is new to the Coursera platform and
這是一個Coursera平台的新功能，
we're going to try it in the next couple of lectures.
我們將在接下來的幾個課程中嘗試一下。
Second, the Coursera system has been integrated with Jupyter notebooks.
其次，Coursera系統已經與Jupyter電腦筆記本相整合。
These notebooks allow you to divide your code up into what they call cells, and
這些電腦筆記本允許你將程式分解為所謂的單元，
execute these cells on demand.
並根據需要執行來這些單元。
The nice thing about these notebook is that they offer a semi-permanent
關於這些電腦筆記本的好處是它們提供了一個半永久性
storage for your learning and you can experiment and
的存儲空間用來學習，你可以進行實驗
play with programming without having to install anything on your computer.
和寫程式，而不需要在電腦上安裝任何東西。
All of the assignments will be done in the Jupiter notebooks but you can of course
所有的作業將在Jupyter筆記本中完成，但你也可以自行
download and install, Python, Jupyter, all of the associated libraries you need for
下載並安裝Python，Jupyter，和所有你需要的，相關的程式庫
this course on your own computer if you'd like.
在你自己的電腦上，如果你比較喜歡。
Our tutorial assistant will provide an overview of this
我們的教程助理將概述這個安裝過程。
process by installing the Jupyter notebooks locally in the next video for
在下一個影片中，如何在你自己的電腦安裝Jupyter電腦筆記本，
those of you who are interested, and I'll give an overview of how you can use these
為那些有興趣的人。我將在課程中概述如何在Coursera環境中
notebooks in the Coursera environment in this lecture.
使用這些電腦筆記本。
But for now, let's dig in to some basic Python.
但現在，讓我們來討論一些基本的Python。
First, Python is a high level language, which means it's optimized for
首先，Python是一種高級程式語言，這意味著它是針對
reading by people instead of machines.
人的能夠理解，而不是機器來進行優化的。
It's also an interpreted language which means it isn't compiled directly to
它也是一種直譯語言，這意味著它不直接編譯為
machine code and importantly is commonly used in an interactive fashion.
機器碼，更重要的是，它通常以互動方式來使用。
This might be quite different if you're used to programming in something like
這可能會有很大差異，如果你習慣於像Java或C這類的程式，
Java or C, where you write your code, compile it, run it, and watch the output.
你寫程式，編譯它，運行並查看它的輸出。
In Python, you can start the interactive interpreter and begin writing code,
在Python中，你可以啟動互動式直譯器，開始編寫程式，
line by line, with the interpreter evaluating each statement as you write it.
直譯器會進行評估你編寫的每一行程式。
This turns out to be very useful for
這是非常有用的，在對於需要大量調查研究的程式工作來說，
tasks that require a lot of investigation, versus those that require a lot of design.
對比於那些先需要大量設計的程式工作。
Shell scripting is one example of this.
Shell腳本就是其中的一個例子。
And data cleaning is another.
數據清理是另一個。
Or you can write scripts that execute programs like you might be
雖然你可以編寫完全的腳本然後執行程式，類似你可能
used to another languages.
用過的其他程式語言，
We're going to use Python throw specialization
但我們在這整個專業化課程中，
in this interactive fashion.
將以這種互動方式來使用Python。
A common surprise for some programmers coming from a Java or C background is that
來自Java或C背景的一些程式設計師的一個共同驚喜是，
Python is a dynamically typed language, similar to languages like JavaScript.
Python是一種動態類型的語言，類似於JavaScript等語言。
This means that when you declare a variable,
這意味著當你聲明一個變數時，
you can assign it to be an integer on one line, and a string on the next line.
你可以在上一行將其指定為整數，並在下一行將其指定為字符串。
Since there is no compilation step,
由於沒有編譯(compile)步驟，
you don't have anyone to help you manage types.
你沒有任何人來幫助你處理變數的類型。
You need to either check for the presence of functionality when you go to use it or
當你使用它時，你需要檢查功能存在與否? 或
try and use the functionality and catch any errors that occur.
嘗試使用其功能，並抓到可能發生的任何錯誤。
The dynamic typing of Python is particularly nice when used in
Python的動態類型是特別有益的，
an interactive fashion, as it allows you to quickly set and
當以互動方式使用時，因為它允許你快速的設置和
modify variable contents without having to worry about the underlying syntactic
修改變量內容，而無需擔心變數的
definition of the variable.
底層語法定義。
Okay, so let's jump in with an example.
好的，我們來舉個例子。
For all of the coded examples I'll show you, you'll find an annotated version of
對於我將向你展示的所有程式例子，你將可以在課程資源的部分
the notebook with more comments in the course resources section.
找到筆記本的註釋版本，而且有更多註解。
You're welcome to follow along with that if you'd like or create a new notebook and
如果你願意，歡迎隨時跟隨那裏，或創建一個新的筆記本，
actively write code, if you prefer.
積極寫程式，如果你喜歡的話。
Python is very little boiler plate code.
Python只有很少的內定程式
In fact, if you just wanted to set the value of a couple of variables, and output
事實上，如果你只想設置一些變數的值，
the results of these variables added together, you could do so in three lines.
並將這些變數加在一起的結果輸出，你可以用三行程式來做。
In this example, I'll write three statements.
在這個例子中，我將寫三個陳述式。
The first two set the variables x and y, each to be some integer value.
前兩個設置變數x和y，每個都是整數值。
Then we'll do some addition.
然後我們做一個加法。
We can run this cell by hitting shift+enter or
我們可以通過點擊shift+enter來運行這個單元，或
by clicking on the play head icon in the tool bar.
點擊工具欄中的'進行'圖示。
The output from the statement is immediately printed.
程式的輸出會立即印出來。
If you were using Python in a non interactive mode, nothing would print.
如果你在非互動模式下使用Python，則不會印出任何結果。
But since we're using it in interactive mode, we get the value immediately.
但是，由於我們以互動模式使用它，我們立即獲得該值。
What's happening underneath is that the browser is sending your Python code
真正發生的是瀏覽器將你的Python程式
across to a machine in the cloud,
發送到雲端中的一台電腦機器，
which executes the code in a Python three interpreter, and sends the results back.
該電腦機器執行Python 3直譯器的代碼，並將結果發送回來。
We can see that after executing a cell, a new empty cell is created for us below.
我們可以看到，在執行一個單元後，下面為我們創建了一個新的空單元。
If we just put in x and execute, we get the value of 1.
如果我們只是放x，然後執行，我們得到的是1.
So it's important to know that the Python interpreter is stateful.
所以重要的是要知道Python直譯器是有狀態的。
That is, that your variables exist between cells.
也就是說，你的變數存在於單元格之間。
Beyond that, if we go back and change something in a previous cell,
除此之外，如果我們回去改變上一個單元中的某些內容，
we have to re-execute the script to make those changes take place.
我們必須重新執行腳本，以使這些更改發生。
The restart and run all function is particularly useful, as it wipes
重新啟動並運行所有功能特別有用，因為它會擦除
the interpreter state and reruns all of the cells in the current notebook.
直譯器狀態，並重新運行當前筆記本中的所有單元。
You'll notice that Python doesn't require the use of
你會注意到，Python不需要使用
keywords like var to declare a variable name or
關鍵字，諸如用var來聲明一個變數名稱，或
semicolons at the end of lines which are commonly used in other languages.
用分號在行末尾，在其他程式語言中常用的。
Python leverages white space to understand the scope of functions and
Python利用空白來理解函數和迴路的範疇，
loops and end of line markers to understand the end of statements.
以及行尾符號來理解程式語句的結尾。
Of course, Python has traditional software structures like functions.
當然，Python具有諸如函數之類的傳統軟體結構。
Here's an example, refactoring that previous code into a function.
這是一個例子，將之前的程式重構成一個函數。
You'll see the deaf statement indicates that we're writing a function.
你會看到'def'語句，表明我們正在寫一個函數。
Then each line that is part of the function needs to be indented
然後作為函數的一部分，每一行都需要
with a tab character or a couple of spaces.
使用製表符(Tab)或縮進幾個空格。
Again, because we're in an interactive environment, when the statement is
再次，因為我們處於互動式的環境中，當程式語句在
evaluated on a shift+enter, the results are printed out immediately below.
shift+enter上進行評估時，結果將在下面立即印出來。
Here's our first bit of interaction.
這是我們第一個互動式程式。
Why don't you try and change this function to accept three parameters instead of two
讓你試試，改變這個函數來接受三個參數而不是兩個，
and return the sum of all three of those.
並返回所有這三個參數的總和。
Okay, functions are great but they're a bit different than you might find in
好的，功能很棒，但是它們有一點不同於
other languages and here are some of subtleties involved.
其他語言，這裡有一些微妙之處。
First, since there's no typing, you don't have to set your return time.
首先，由於沒有類型，你不需要設置返回的類型。
Second, you don't have to set user return statement at all actually.
其次，你實際上不必使用return語句。
There's a special value called none that's returned.
有一個名為'None'的特殊值返回。
None a similar to null in Java and represents the absence of value.
None與Java中的null類似，表示缺少或者沒有值。
Third, in Python, you can have default values for parameters.
第三，在Python中，你可以設置參數的預設值。
Here's an example.
這裡有個例子，這裡有個例子，
In this example, we can rewrite the add numbers function to take three parameters,
在這個例子中，我們可以重寫add_numbers函數來接受三個參數，
but we could set the last parameter to be none by default.
但我們可以設最後的參數 為預設的 None
This means that you can call add numbers with just two values or with three, and
這意味著你可以使用兩個值或三個值來調用add_numbers，而
you don't have to rewrite the function signature to overload it.
不必重寫函數來重載(Overloading)它。
This is an important implication.
這裡有一個重要的暗示含義。
All of the optional parameters, the ones that you got default values for,
所有可選用的參數，那些有預設值的，
need to come at the end of the function declaration.
都需要放在函數聲明的最末尾。
It also means that you can pass an optional parameters as labeled values.
這也意味著你可以傳遞可選參數為一個標記值。
Here's an example of a labeled parameters.
以下是有標記參數的例子。
We can rewrite that function so that there's two optional parameters.
我們可以重寫該函數，以便有兩個可選參數。
If we want to call the function with just two numbers but
如果我們只用兩個數字來呼叫該函數，但也
also set the flag value, we have to explicitly name and
設置了標記值，我們必須有明確地資料名稱，
set the flag parameter to true when invoking the function.
並將已標記的參數設置為True時，來調用該函數。
By now, you've also seen the use of the print statement.
到現在，你也看到了使用print語句。
We're going to dive into strings in more detail, but
我們將更詳細地介紹'字串'(strings)，
print will take an item, try and convert it to a string and print the output.
print將會拿一個項目，嘗試將其轉換為字串，然後輸出。
We don't use this much in the interactive mode of the interpreter, but
我們不會在直譯器的互動模式中使用這麼多print，但是
it's useful when we want to print out multiple values for a single cell.
當我們要從單一個單元格來印出多個輸出值時，這很有用。
Okay, a final word on the basics of functions in Python.
好的，關於基本的Python函數最後一句話。
In Python, you can assign a variable to a function.
在 Python 中，可以將一個變數分配給一個函數。
This might seem either completely normal to you or
這可能看起來完全正常，或
completely odd depending upon on your programming background.
完全奇怪，取決於你的編寫程式背景。
By assigning a variable to a function, you can pass that variable into
通過指定一個函數到一個變數，你可以將該變數傳遞給
other functions allowing some basic functional programming.
其他函數，這會允許一些基本的功能程式。
We'll talk about that a little bit later on in the course.
我們會在稍後課程再談一談。
But here's an example where we define a function to add numbers,
這裡是一個例子，我們定義一個函數來加數字，
then we assign that function to a variable, and then we invoke the variable.
然後我們將該函數賦給一個變數，然後我們調用該變數。